谢谢你昨晚守夜
Thanks for keeping watch last night.
没事  我喜欢
Oh, it's nothing. I like it.
今晚你来守吧
Uh, you can keep watch tonight.
我们今天会有收获吗
We gonna win today?
会的
Oh, yeah.
我们也需要给那个对讲机找电池
We're gonna need batteries for that walkie, too.
让它重新开始工作
Get it working again.
怎么了  笑什么
What is it? What's that smile?
我们出来几天了  结果只找到
Couple of days out, all we got to show are
差不多两把枪  几个压扁的豆子罐头
two guns, dented cans of beans,
和几件球衣
and some football jerseys, pretty much.
差不多吧
Pretty much.
我们在抗争
We're fightin' the fight.
这样更好
It's better.
早上好
Good morning.
如果我再听见关于肥乔的一个字
And if I hear one more goddamn word about Fat Joey,
我就打碎某人的牙齿
I'm gonna smash somebody's teeth in.
我看是甩掉了累赘
Good riddance to dead weight.
总算没什么狗屁吉祥物了
No more mascot crap.
他们对椒盐脆饼的品位不错
They got good taste in pretzels.
还有电池
And batteries.
两天了  我们得回去了
Two days. We're gonna need to get back.
瑞克
Rick...
再过一天半  今天和明天
Day and a half more -- today and tomorrow.
我们可以再出来  我们应该回去了
We can come out again. We should get back.
再转会儿
Just a little more.
我们没事
We're okay.
我们没必要现在就找到武器
We don't have to find them right now.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
再转转吧
Just a little more, okay?
好
Okay.
《行尸走肉》
我正想来拆线
Hey, I was just coming over to do that.
丹妮斯教过我
Denise showed me how.
我弄完了
I'm done.
怎么了
What?
没什么
Nothing.
好吧
Okay.
会解决的
It's gonna work out.
那是什么意思  塔拉
What -- What does that even mean, Tara?
意思是我们现在有足够的人手去战斗了
It means we've got the numbers to fight now.
我们只用找一些枪
We just need to find some guns and --
你知道我们今天能在哪找到这么多枪吗
Do you know where we could find that many guns today?
这周呢  今年呢
This week? This year?
你不知道
No. You don't.
我不能就这样等着
I can't just wait.
我不知道你  但我不行
I don't know about you, but I can't.
我们会找到枪的  好吗  我们会战斗的
We're gonna find the guns, okay? And we're gonna fight.
这肯定不容易
Look, it's not gonna be easy.
不像上次哨站那样
It wasn't the last time at the outpost.
也许你可以省点脾气跟他们打
Hey, maybe you could just save all this for them.
给
Here.
能帮你的伤疤愈合
It'll help with your scar.
你留着吧
Keep it.
我们需要枪
We need guns.
我要去找
I'm gonna go find them.
该死
Damn it.
怎么了
What was it?
是一头鹿
It was a deer.
我欠你一头鹿
I owe you a deer.
之前那次
From before.
那时他们在门外
When they were outside the gate.
是啊
Oh, yeah, you do.
看见了吗
You see that?
嗯
Yeah.
这种枪就是我们出来要找的
It's guns like that. That's why we're out here.
这里发生了惨剧
Something serious happened here.
很久以前
A long time ago.
是啊  这些子弹很不错
Yeah. These are serious rounds.
也许这里也有好枪
Might be serious guns here, too.
我们仔细瞧瞧
Let's get a better look.
好
Yeah.
该死
Damn it.
注意脚下
Watch your step.
也许我们不该在这里待太久
Maybe we shouldn't be up here too long.
我们去看看有什么吧
Well, let's see what we're gonna see.
士兵  平民  这些子弹
Soldiers, civilians, all those rounds --
曾有一场恶战
There was a fight.
也许是行尸
Maybe it was the walkers.
也许是别的人
Maybe just other people.
他们还背着枪
They're still wearing their guns.
我觉得就是这里了
I think this is it.
我也这么想
I think it is, too.
觉得我们可以搞定吗
Think we can?
可以的
Yeah, we can.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事  你呢
Y-Yeah. Are you?
我没事
I am.
这是个预兆  对吧
This is -- This is a sign, right?
是的  肯定是
This is it. It has to be.
的确是
Oh-ho. It is.
(即食口粮)
它们是即食的
Well, they're ready.
我们吃吧
Let's eat.
我没找到枪
I didn't find any guns.
如果你想知道的话
In case you were wondering.
我在外面找了一整天  一把都没找到
I was out there all day and not a damn one.
一把真枪都没找到
Not a real one.
问题是  我之前有一把枪
Thing is, I had a gun.
我本来打算用它杀了尼根
I was gonna use it to kill Negan.
我都已经准备好了
I was ready to.
假如我当时成功了  像我计划中的那样
And if I had done it, like I'd planned to,
那如今尼根已经死了
Negan would be dead right now.
没错  也许我也会死  但谁他妈在乎
And, yeah, maybe I'd be dead, too, but who gives a damn?
那样的话尤金就不会被抓走
Eugene would still be here.
奥利维亚会还活着
Olivia would still be alive.
斯宾塞也会还活着
Spencer would still be alive.
但如今他们都不在了  而我却还在
And now they're gone, and I'm here
就因为我愚蠢地听信了你的话
because I was stupid enough to listen to you.
但你听了
But you were.
也照做了
And you did.
你就站在那里对别人指手画脚
You stand there telling people about their lives.
只对那些来这里的人
Only if they come here.
比如你
Like you.
就像现在
Right now.
你什么都不懂
You don't know shit about shit.
你说得对
You're right.
我的确不懂
I don't.
我说过你不应该去送死
I said that you weren't supposed to die
不应该去做那件你计划要做的事
and that you shouldn't do the thing that you were planning to do
因为我们需要你
because we needed you --
我们如今依然需要
still do.
像我这样的傻瓜都能看清那一点
Even a fool like me could see that.
死了的确会更容易些
It's easier to be dead,
假如你还活着是我的错的话
and if it's my fault you're alive,
那我只能背负着这个错误了
well, I'm just gonna have to live with that.
我当时决定要插手
I decided to meddle.
但我做的是我认为正确的事
But I did something I thought was right,
我也知道这事风险很大
and I knew the stakes were very high.
你当然可以因为自己还活着而指责我
You can certainly blame me for the fact that you have a life,
但之后呢  你要怎么办
but after that what are you going to do with it?
你要如何促成那些必须得发生的事
How are you going to make what needs to happen happen?
在你心跳停止之前  一切皆有可能
Anything is possible until your heart stops beating.
你能做的绝不仅仅是冲着个傻子大吼
Certainly more than yelling at a fool.
(美国政府财产  严禁商业转售)
(即食口粮  7号菜单  牛腩配肉汁)
(火鸡胸肉)
什么
What?
如何
How is it?
棒极了
It's good.
所以  明天...
So, tomorrow...
我们出去  把武器抢回来  对吗
we go out there, we get the weapons, right?
然后让简迪斯和她的人和我们一起战斗
We get Jadis and her people to fight with us.
我们杀死尼根
We kill Negan
以及其他该杀之人  来赢得战斗
and anyone else we have to to win.
在那之后呢
And what happens after that?
之后  我们继续生活
After that, we keep going.
是的  但是
Yeah, but...
尼根用他的方法统治世界
Negan ordered the world his way.
他死之后  我们应该建立新秩序  对吧
It's up to us to reorder it once he's gone, right?
所有社区
All the different communities,
可以一起想办法  谈论如何继续生活
they can figure it out together, how to keep going together.
对  但总得有人促成这事
Yeah, but somebody's gonna have to make that happen.
总得有人负责  对吗
Somebody will need to be in charge of that, right?
这个人应该是你
It should be you.
-不是我  -为什么
- Not me. - ‭Why not?
你可以胜任的
You could do it.
你会做得很好
‭You'd be good at it.
如果你想做的话
I mean, if it's something that you wanted.
我不想做  也不愿意做
Well, I don't think I do. Or I would.
但如果是咱们俩  你和我
But the two of us, you and me,
一起重建秩序
reordering things together...
那我愿意
I want that.
假如你也愿意的话...
If it's something you wanted....
我愿意
Yeah.
我要再吃五包这个  好吗
I'm gonna eat five more of these dinners, okay?
知道吗
You know...
我们用不着明天就搞定
we don't have to get it done tomorrow.
我们可以悠闲点
We can take our time.
过一两天再走也没关系
If we go another day, another one after that, it's fine.
我是说  这地方没危险
I mean, the place is clear.
严严实实的
It's locked up tight.
只有一条路能进来  所以
We found the only way in, so...
我们得回去
We should get back.
既然能拿到枪
If we're getting the guns,
多花点时间也没关系
it doesn't matter if it takes a little longer.
等等  我一直
Wait. I've been, um...
在等着给你看这个
I've been waiting to show you this one.
这可是  辣椒  奶酪意面
It's, um, chili and mac and cheese...
大杂烩
together.
试试吧
Come on.
抱歉
Oh. Sorry.
我在思考
I was just thinking.
什么  你要这个
W..you...you want this?
恭喜
Congrats.
归你了
It's yours.
是别人送我的  曾经帮助过我的某人
Someone gave it to me, someone who helped me.
她为我不顾一切
She put her ass on the line for me.
她救了我的命  知道吗
She saved my life, you know?
她本来不用的  但却做了
She didn't have to. But she did.
如今这样做是有意义的  毋庸置疑
That means something now -- it does. It has to.
要是我说了  知道吗
If I say something, you know --
拿不到枪  瑞克是不会离开那里的
Rick won't leave there without their guns.
就算我们能成功接近那里
If -- if we could even get close enough,
她们也会开火  我们会反击
they'll start firing, and we'll fire back.
她们应该跟我们并肩战斗的
I mean, they should just fight with us.
救世军杀了她们的父亲
The Saviors killed their fathers
儿子和兄弟
and their sons and their brothers.
但她们不会想和我们并肩战斗的
They won't want to fight with us.
她们只想藏起来
They just want to hide.
所以她们只能和我们战斗
So they'll just fight us.
如果我告诉大家海边旅馆的事  就会这样
I tell everyone about Oceanside, that's what happens.
凭什么我们的命比他们的更珍贵
What makes our life worth more than theirs?
就因为我们想阻止
Because we want to stop
那些伤害我们的人吗
the people that are hurting us,
那些会伤害别人的人吗
who will hurt other people?
该死
God damn it.
看
Look.
行尸在外游荡  没有被关起来
The walkers in the field, they're not closed in.
是啊
Yeah.
我们得干掉外面的这些
We got to take care of the ones out here
把缺口堵上  然后再慢慢干掉剩下的
and block that gap, too, so we can take the rest slow.
七  八...
Seven, eight...
九
nine...
那辆车  我能堵上
That car -- I can block it up.
我能干掉挡路的那一个
I can take out that one on the way.
你把剩下的引开
You draw the rest.
你给我留了八个
You're leaving me eight.
我们可以朝它们开枪
We could shoot them,
但这样会引来剩余的行尸
but that would call the rest from the field.
得悄悄行动  用剑
This is about doing it quiet, with the sword.
八个对你来说不是问题
You can handle eight.
你已经干掉八个行尸了  我推得动
You got your eight walkers. I can push.
我也行
So can I.
你只要负责把车开到缺口那儿就行
You just worry about steering us in that gap.
该死
‭Shit.
刹车坏了
The brakes don't work.
米琼恩  你没事吧
Michonne, you good?
没事
Yeah.
你呢
You?
没事
Yeah.
我觉得我们开过头了
I think we overshot it.
你觉得还是你确定
You think or you know?
我确定
I know.
不过这个计划是好的
It was a good plan, though.
这个计划超棒
It was a great plan.
就在这里吧
We'll do it here.
好
Yeah.
该死  这拦不住它们
Shit. It's not gonna hold.
过来了
There it goes!
我们散开  减少它们的数量
Split them off into smaller groups.
栅栏也许能挡住
The barriers might hold.
你去滑梯  我去摩天轮
You take slide, I take Ferris wheel?
或者我们可以逃
Or we could just go.
- 你想逃吗  - 不  我们能搞定
- You want to go?  - Nah. We can do this.
我知道我们能
Yeah, I know we can.
你那边如何
How you doing?!
还剩八个
Eight more!
你呢
How about you?
十个
10!
瑞克
Rick!
米琼恩
Michonne!
我试过了  但我还欠你一头
I tried, but I still owe you one.
我可以在外面多待几天
I could've gone a couple more days.
我喜欢那样
I would've liked that.
我一直没睡
I haven't been sleeping.
想着我们失去了什么
Thinking about what we lost.
想着我的朋友们
Thinking about my friends.
格伦救过我
Glenn saved me.
在最开始的时候
Right at the start.
而我没能救他
I couldn't save him.
这很正常
It's normal.
我知道
I know that.
无法释怀
Being stuck on it.
我们经历了一些事
We went through something.
光这样是不能释怀的
This -- This doesn't cure it.
瑞克  我很抱歉
Rick, I'm sorry.
我们要反抗他们
We're gonna fight them.
这就是接下来会发生的事
That's what happens next.
我们会失去一些人
And we're gonna lose people,
也许是很多人  也许是对方
maybe a lot of them, maybe even each other.
即使那样  也值得
Even then, it'll be worth it.
当我想到...
When I thought that...
我不能失去你
I can't lose you.
你问过我
You asked me
放弃投降算怎么个活法
what kind of life we had just surrendering.
那不是生活
It wasn't -- It wasn't a life.
我们在那里做的事
What we did back there,
我们现在做的事
what we're doing now,
为朱迪思拼未来
making a future for Judith
为格伦和玛姬的孩子拼未来
and for Glenn and Maggie's baby,
做出抗争  这才叫生活
fighting the fight, that's living.
这是你让我知道的
You showed me that.
你可以失去我
You can lose me.
-不  -你可以
- No. - ‭Yes, you can.
我也可以失去你
I can lose you.
我们可以失去朋友  爱的人
We can lose our friends, people we love.
这不再是关乎我们了
It's not about us anymore.
是关乎未来
It's about a future.
如果我没能活下来
And if it's me who doesn't make it,
你就必须带领其他人前行
you're gonna have to lead the others forward
因为你有这能力
because you're the one who can.
但是
But...
你怎么知道
how do you know?
因为
Because...
你带我走到了这里
you led me here.
全都能用吗
Operational? All?
据我说知  能
To the best of my knowledge, yeah.
可能需要清理一下  我们找到了物资
May need some cleaning. We found supplies.
要我们清理吗
Expect us?
我们清理了一部分  上了油
We cleaned some. We oiled some.
剩下的你们来  我们是合作关系
You can do the rest. We do this together.
好的  但能用吗
Yes, yes, but operational?
你可以开几枪试试  如果你想的话
Well, you can fire a few. Try them out, if you like.
-多少把  -63把
- How many? - 63.
我们做了清单
We made an inventory.
不
No.
你是说不要清单吗
You mean the inventory?
-不够  -你说什么
- Not enough. - ‭What are you talking about?
你要很多枪  这就是很多枪
You asked for a lot of guns. That's what this is.
要为你战斗  我们需要两倍的枪
Enough to fight your fight. Us? Nearly twice.
需要两倍的枪
Need nearly twice.
我们浪费够多时间了
We've wasted enough time.
走吧  带上枪
Let's go. Take our guns with us.
不行
No.
这是我们的枪  协议还没结束
Our guns to take. Our deal still on.
你们不能全拿
Not all of them.
我们留十把  为了找更多的枪
We're keeping 10 for ourselves -- to find more.
五把
Five.
-十把  -六把
- 10. - ‭6.
-十把  -九把
- 10. - ‭9.
而且要归还猫
And the cat back.
二十把  猫归我
20. I keep the cat.
我们给你找到枪  然后一起战斗
We get you the guns. We fight together.
说同意
Say yes.
同意
Yes.
尽快拿来更多枪  我们就战斗
More soon, we'll fight.
再多等几天
You get a few more days
"接下来的事"就会发生
before "What happens next."
再多等几天
Few more days?
没错
That's right.
我们会找到更多枪  想办法解决
We'll find more, figure it out.
很快的
Soon.
再多等几天
In a few more days.
你没事吧
You all right?
没事  我只是...正准备去找你
Yeah, yeah, I was just -- I was just coming over to see you.
怎么了
What's up?
你见到罗西塔了吗
Have you seen Rosita?
今早换岗她不在
She didn't show for her guard shift this morning.
她大概出去找枪了吧
She probably just went out looking for more.
好吧
Mm. Yeah.
你为什么...
Why were you --
你为什么找我
Why were you coming by?
我要告诉你一些事
I have something to tell you.
你来这里是...
Are you here --
我来这里是找你帮忙的
I'm here because I need your help.
有一个条件
One condition --
要由我杀他
I get to take the shot.
好
Okay.
你带桥上的炸药了吗
Did you bring any explosives from the bridge?
我考虑过
I thought about it.
但我不想被别人发现和阻止
But I didn't want anyone finding out and trying to stop me.
我带了更好的东西
I got something better, though.
这样你就能杀他了
So you can take your shot.
瑞克和米琼恩找到了枪
Rick and Michonne found guns.
但他们没准备好行动
But they aren't ready to move.
他们不能
They can't.
她们需要更多枪  更多人  更多时间
The need more guns, more people, more time,
更多借口
more excuses.
我记下了达里尔和卡尔给瑞克说的
I memorized everything Daryl and Carl told Rick
尼根基地内部情况
about the inside of Negan's place.
耶稣给我画了一张外围的地图
Jesus made me a map of the outside.
非常远  守卫森严
It's far away. It's well-defended.
-只有我们两个人  -你要改主意吗
There's only two of us. You changing your mind?
我准备好杀他了
I'm ready to kill him.
但我要确认你知道这意味着什么
But I need to make sure you know what this means.
你知道吗
Do you?
他们不能活捉我们
They can't catch us alive.
如果被抓住  就给了他们借口
If they do, we give them something.
我们这是有去无回
It's a one-way ticket for both of us.
假如我们都去的话
If it is both of us.
我们都去
It is.